[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The human heart has its own automation but its activity is regulated by the needs of the whole body. The nerves which accelerate the heart rate are called parasympathetic.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do the tattoos on Jesse and Chesters backs say in the 2000 comedy movie Dude, Wheres My Car?", "correct_answer": "Dude and sweet", "incorrect_answers": ["Eat and sleep", "Chicks and dudes", "Kitty and Bunny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How oblate is Saturn?", "correct_answer": ".1", "incorrect_answers": [".07", ".11", ".08"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the oldest of Benjamin Martins children from the movie The Patriot?", "correct_answer": "Gabriel", "incorrect_answers": ["Susan", "Nathan", "Thomas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to legend, each leaflet of a 4-leaf clover has a meaning. What does the 1st leaf mean?", "correct_answer": "Hope", "incorrect_answers": ["Luck", "Strength", "Prosperity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies is an all time favorite about a romance during World War II and stars film legends Humphrey Bogart and Ingrid Bergman?", "correct_answer": "Casablanca", "incorrect_answers": ["Paths of Glory", "Tokyo Story", "From Here to Eternity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The expression badgering someone\u201d came from the cruel sport of badger baiting.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unusual physical characteristic does the lemur Aye-aye possess?", "correct_answer": "It has extremely long fingers.", "incorrect_answers": ["Its pupils are constantly dilated.", "It has 4 nipples.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The production of the hormone melatonin is inhibited by light and permitted by darkness. In which part of the body is it produced?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Gastrointestinal tract", "Retina", "Pineal gland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word is a collective noun, which means a group of ferrets.", "correct_answer": "fesnyng", "incorrect_answers": ["bevy", "charm", "leash"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the full name of Demi Moores character in the film St. Elmos Fire?", "correct_answer": "Jules Jacoby", "incorrect_answers": ["Jules Johnson", "Jules Johannsen", "Jules Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bergamot oil was discovered by this great explorer, born in Genoa, the son of a wool merchant and weaver.", "correct_answer": "Christopher Columbus", "incorrect_answers": ["Amerigo Vespucci", "Fernando Magelan", "Marco Polo"]}]